Guide to the Foster Hall Collection Curatorial Correspondence, 1825-1981 CAM.FHCCC.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 86:1
  - Correspondence, 1825-1978; 1939-1969; III.
    - Stephen Foster Memorial Commission, White Springs, Florida, 1950 - [1967-1969] - 1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 253)
    - Stephen Foster Memorial Commission, White Springs, Florida, Anniversary Celebrations, 1951, 1957 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 254)
    - Stephen Foster Memorial Commission, White Springs, Florida, Publications, 1960 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 255)
    - Steuben Glass, 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 256)
    - Su-Sw, 1938-1940, 1955-1967 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 257)
    - Ta-Th, 1941-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 258)
    - Thorton, William Foster, 1941, 1944 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 259)
    - Ti-Tr, 1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 2, Folder 260)
    - Tioga Point Museum, 1939, [1941-1942] - 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 261)
    - Ts-Ty, 1945-1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 262)
    - Townsend, John Wilson, 1939-1956, 1965-1966, 1970 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 263)
    - Transfer of Foster Collection, 1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 264)
    - Tuesday Musical Club, Executive Building Committee, Minutes, 1932-1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 266)
    - Tuesday Musical Club, Correspondence of the Executive Building Committee, 1933-1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 267)
    - U-V, 1939-1957, 1965-1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 268)
    - University Announcements, 1941-1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 269)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Fitzgerald, R., 1947-1949, [1950, 1954] (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 270)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Rankin, Allen C., 1961-[1964]-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 271)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Rupp, G.S., 1941 - [1945] - 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 272)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Rupp, G.S., 1953-1959, 1964 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 273)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Rush, Hellen P., 1938-1939, 1965 - [1968] (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 274)
    - University of Pittsburgh, General 1, 1950-1956 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 275)
    - University of Pittsburgh, General 2, [1939] - 1960 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 276)
    - University of Pittsburgh, General 3, 1950, [1965] (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 277)
    - University of Pittsburgh, General 4, 1950-1960 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 278)
    - University of Pittsburgh, General 5, 1938-1970 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 279)
    - University of Pittsburgh Press, 1937-1949, 1959 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 280)
    - U.s. Postage Stamp, 1939-1941 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 281)
    - Veteran's Administration, 1948, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 282)
    - Vidas, Raoul Georges, 1939, 1945-1946 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 283)
    - Wa, 1944-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 284)
    - Washington Memorial, Commission of Fine Arts, 1949-1951 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 285)
    - Washington Memoral, Congress, 1949 - [1950] (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 286)
    - Washington Memorial, Niehaus Statue, 1951-1952 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 287)
    - Washington Memorial, Location, 1951 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 288)
    - Washington Memorial, Unveiling, 1952-1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 289)
    - We, 1939-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 290)
    - Webb, Anna H., 1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 291)
    - Wh-Wi, 1940-1968 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 292)
    - Whitlock's, Inc., [1942], 1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 293)
    - Wigmore, S.J., 1941-1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 294)
    - Wignore, S.J., 1952-1963 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 295)
    - Wilson, Mary A., 1942, [1945-1947], 1954-1957 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 296)
    - Wilt, L.E., 1941-1952 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 297)
    - Wo-Wy, 1940-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 298)
    - Wright, Edith A., 1940-1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 299)
    - Y-Z, 1940-1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 300)
    - Young, David, [1940-1949] - 1955 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 3, Folder 301)
  - Financial Documents, 1938-1970, 1979-1981; IV.
    This series consists of financial statements and account documents related to the collection.
    - Donor's Lists, 1957 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 302)
    - Financial Statements, 1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 302)
    - Financial Statements, 1939 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 304)
    - Financial Statements, 1940 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 305)
    - Financial Statements, 1941 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 306)
    - Financial Statements, 1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 307)
    - Financial Statements, 1943 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 308)
    - Financial Statements, 1944 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 309)
    - Financial Statements, 1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 310)
    - Financial Statements, 1946 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 311)
    - Financial Statements, 1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 312)
    - Financial Statements, 1948 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 313)
    - Financial Statements, 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 314)
    - Financial Statements, 1966 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 315)
    - University of Pittsburgh Accounting System Reports, 1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 316)
    - University of Pittsburgh Accounting System Reports, 1977 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 317)
    - University of Pittsburgh Accounting System Reports, 1978 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 318)
    - University of Pittsburgh Accounting System Reports, 1980 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 319)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Reports, 1942-1981 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 320)
    - Lilly Medal Presentation, Financial Transactions, 1940 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 321)
  - Inquiries, 1947, 1950; V.
    This series consists of correspondence requesting specific publications generated by the collection.
    - Request for Material, 1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 322)
    - Request for material, A-F, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 323)
    - Request for Material, G-L, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 324)
    - Request for Material, M-R, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 325)
    - Request for Material, S-Z, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 326)
- 86:2 Fine Arts Committee of the Civic Club of Allegheny County Records, 1913, 1923-1955; 1.5 Cubic Feet
  - General Correspondence, 1913, 1923-1955; 0.5 Cubic Feet
    - Agendas, 1930-1939 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 1)
    - Agendas, 1940-1944, 1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 2)
    - Foster Promotion Elsewhere, 1923 - [1941-1943] (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 3)
    - Foster Memorial, 1927-1929 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
    - Highland Park Monument Restoration, 1937-1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 5)
    - Highland Park Monument Restoration contributions, 1937-1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 6)
    - Highland Park Monument Move to Oakland, [1940]-1944, 1955 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 7)
    - Hall of Fame, 1940-1941 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 8)
    - ASAP Award, [1940-1942]-1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 9)
    - Radio Broadcasts, 1934-1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 1923-1944 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 11)
    - Articles, Speeches, Programs, 1913, 1926-1934, 1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1924, 1928, 1930-1939 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 13)
  - Commemoration Files, 1923-1956; 1 Cubic Feet
    - History of Commemoration Services, 1935 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 14)
    - Commemoration, 1923 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 15)
    - Commemoration, 1924 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 16)
    - Commemoration, 1925 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 17)
    - Commemoration, 1927 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 18)
    - Commemoration, 1928 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 19)
    - Commemoration, 1929 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 20)
    - Commemoration, 1930 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 21)
    - Commemoration, 1931 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 22)
    - Commemoration, 1932 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 23)
    - Commemoration, 1933 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 24)
    - Commemoration, 1934 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 25)
    - Commemoration, 1935 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 26)
    - Commemoration, 1936 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 27)
    - Commemoration, 1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 28)
    - Foster Calendar Day, 1937-1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 29)
    - Commemoration, 1938 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 30)
    - Commemoration, 1939 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 31)
    - Commemoration, 1940 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 32)
    - Commemoration, 1941 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 33)
    - Commemoration, 1942 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 34)
    - Commemoration, 1943 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 35)
    - Commemoration, 1944 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 36)
    - Commemoration, 1945 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 37)
    - Commemoration, 1946 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 38)
    - Commemoration, 1947 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 39)
    - Commemoration, 1948 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 40)
    - Commemoration, 1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 41)
    - Commemoration, 1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 42)
    - Commemoration, 1951 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 43)
    - Commemoration, 1952 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 44)
    - Commemoration, 1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 45)
    - Commemoration, 1954 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 46)
    - Commemoration, 1955-1956 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 6, Folder 47)